Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1965-1966; 1969-2006; 12; 30.75 cubic ft.
  - Subseries D: Books, 1966; 1970; 1973; 1977; 1982; 1989-1990; 1992-1993; 1996; 1998; 2000-2001; 2005-2006; 1 cubic feet
    Lewis, Matthew B. The Monk, 1977 printing. Heavily annotated by Geof Huth.
    Loose Watch: A Lost and Found Times Anthology, 1998. Includes three pieces by Geof Huth.
    O'Connor, Flannery. Wise Blood, 1973 printing. Annotated by Geof Huth.
    Saper, Craig J. Networked Art, 2001. Includes a four-page discussion of Geof Huth's micropress, dbqp.
    Schmidt, S. J., ed. ersichlichkeiten: internationale visuelle texte der 90er, 1996. Includes reproductions of a number of issues of dbqp and of a concrete poem manuscript by Geof Huth from 1986.
    Stevens, Wallace. The Collected Poems, 1982. Heavily annotated by Geof Huth during a class taken with Phillip Booth in the early 1980s.